Hey, congratulations. What, what does
this mean to you? And did you have any
idea that the Saints were a team that
you could end up with?
Yeah, this means everything, man. I'm
ready to give, you know, this whole this
organization my all. I'm just super
excited.
Talked to Saints a little bit.
Both at the combine and and and
was really, you know, happy with my
experience with them and and the
coaching staff. So, I'm super excited.
Bryce, you obviously already have a
brother who's been through the process.
What did he tell you about it?
Uh yeah, honestly about this whole
process,
um
you know, he just told me to be myself.
You know, he knows I'm a hard worker, a
a good person, a genuine dude.
So, he just, you know, let me let me
know that God's got God's got going to
handle the rest and you know, I I just
got to just got to do me.
What is it about the North Dakota State
program that produces so many of you NFL
guys?
Yeah, you know, we've been in FCS all
these years, but I really don't think
you compare us to, you know, average FCS
program. We hold ourselves to a really
high standard. The standard is a
national championship. You know, I don't
care what level that is. That's a hard
thing to do. So,
like I said, we hold ourselves to a
really hard standard and we pride
ourselves on, you know, doing the doing
doing the hard work and all the little
things, you know, to to to achieve a
championship. Bryce, couple of
questions. Do you know any players on
the Saints team and are you familiar
with the city of New Orleans? Have you
been here?
Uh never been to to the city, no.
But I've been a big fan fan of the
receiver room, Chris, especially and all
the things he's done.
So, I'm super excited to learn from him
and just compete every day.
Bryce, how much of an influence did your
brother have on you? What was it like
growing up together?
Yeah, a ton, a ton. That's my best
friend. That's my guy. You know, he's
he's got me
for life and I got both the football
side and the business side of things.
So,
he's he's played a very large part in my
journey.
What did it mean to you to run a 4-3 at
the combine and
were you expecting to run that?
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I was expecting to
run
low 4-3s.
I was super happy with the way the
combine performance turned out. I pride
myself on hard work, like I said
earlier. So, just that whole combine
prep time
and just grinded. So, I was happy with
the results.
What strengths What do you feel like are
your strengths as a receiver and and
what areas would you like to work on?
Yeah, for sure. I think
um
>> [clears throat]
>> receiver-wise, I think I have elite ball
skills. You know, when the ball's in the
air, it's mine or nobody's. Um that's
something I always pride myself on. Um
I think I play the game at a really fast
pace. Um I think I learn really quick. I
can read defenses, things like that.
Um I think, you know, the receiver
position is a super technical position.
So, I think I can get better at the
technical aspects of that.
Um I'm super excited to learn from those
guys and and and coach and um just to
improve overall.
How were you as a blocker?
Oh, great. We we at NDSU, you don't play
if you can't block. So, that that that
that was that was my role for a while.
How much contact did you have with
with coach Keith Williams in particular,
the the wide receiver coach? And and
what were your impressions of him?
Yeah, met him for the first time at the
combine. Had a formal interview with
them.
And
super impressed with him. And now I'm
super excited to learn from him.
It was they were my first formal
interview. So,
didn't really know what to expect at
first, but I can already tell, you know,
he's going he's going to teach me a lot
and and we're going to get along just
fine. Have you talked to Trey since you
were picked?
Yes, sir. Yeah, he's here. He he he was
right beside me. So, he's pumped. Saints
have been doing a lot of work on the
offensive side of the ball throughout
this draft class. Just, you know, what
does it
what does it say to you that they've
included you as a part of the, you know,
clear
endeavor of adding more playmakers to
this offense?
Yeah, means everything. You know, all it
takes is one. And the fact that these
guys believe in me and this coaching
staff believes in me. Um I'm ready to
earn earn that trust and earn that
belief, honestly, with both the coaching
staff and my teammates as well.
Um like I said, you know, the goal is
championships and you know, that's
that's what I'm bringing.
Uh you know, my desire to win
championships to this organization.
You know, there aren't there aren't a
lot of domes in college, but you know,
the Fargo Dome is is kind of unique.
Um does does that help at all? Just
being
familiar with a dome setting as you come
here to play in the Superdome?
Yeah, I think for sure. I mean, I've
played in all sorts of stadiums,
obviously, but
yeah, I think playing in a dome
definitely has its benefits, you know,
to correlating to playing in another
dome, for sure. Just the lighting and
things like that. So,
Are you excited to make the leap from
Minnesota and North Dakota to a warmer
climate? Yeah. Yeah, no doubt. You know,
throughout this draft process, you know,
people were asking me where you want to
go and I just remember saying, you know,
somewhere warm wouldn't be too bad.
Somewhere warm wouldn't be too bad. So,
that's an added benefit, you know, to to
my situation. You got warm for sure. I
can promise you
>> [laughter and clears throat]